so I was a victim of uh covid-19 in the
second wave and I got hospitalized as
well in my absence I wanted to make sure
that my family has that Financial
stability thus my journey with Aditya
Sun Life Insurance began so there are a
couple of reasons the first one being
the brand ad Vera Capital has a legacy
to it second being the online portal it
is very seamless and easy to use and you
can make hassle-free payment third being
health benefits it also has access to
health related options which help you
monitor your daily steps and also give
you health returns and commitment last
but not the least the service this is
the most important benefit my adviser
has been guiding us for over a decade
and she always has our best interest in
our mind ad sunlife insurance has my
highest recommendation thank you adilla
capital and thank you ad Sun Life
Insurance
[Music]